RG 003, Litchfield County, County Court Files
Connecticut State Library
Mary Goodwin, a minor, and her father Thomas, sued over tales of her misbehavior at a dance held at Elihu Harrison's house in Litchfield in 1781. It was said that Mary had allowed David Harrison, Solomon Woodruff and John Woodruff to "debauch her chastity." Not so, say the plaintiffs. The young men, "instigated by … mear malice," "put into a Bowl of Toddy a quantity of Cantharides or Spanish flies and gave the same to the Plt to drink of... to deprive [her] of her reason that they might accomplish the vile purposes of their Heart." Chastity, for a young girl who relied on marriage to provide for her future, was her most valuable commodity, to be protected at all costs, in court if not at dances.
For a businessman like David Buell, to be considered guilty of the "detestable crime of dishonesty" was to lose his livelihood. So when Edward Phelps questioned his integrity by publicly denouncing Buell in 1772, saying "he has no more honesty than the Devil nor never had [,] his Books are as false as the Alkoran," he filed suit and was successful.
Similarly, Robert Livingston Jr., of the Manor Livingston in Albany County, New York sued George Caldwell of Salisbury because the latter called him a rogue and knave who starved the workers at his ironworks and cheated them out of their wages. Justice of the Peace William Kellogg of Cornwall brought suit against Harley R. Ludington for saying that he "gave judgment in Catlin's favor because he owed Catlin for a hat." And Ephraim Hinman, brigadier general of the 8th Connecticut regiment, was said to be taking payoffs to grant discharges from military service, including silver spoons and a Merino ram Even the clergy were not immune. Rev. Samuel Whittlesey of Washington was said by Lewis Ford to be a thief: "I caught a man last night stealing [my] hens... it was Parson Whittlesey... should like [him] better if he would keep out of my hen roost.
Of course, success in a defamation case might not repair the plaintiff's reputation. Consider the suit of Elijah and Betsy Warner of Kent against John and Lydia Hopson. The Warners asserted that Lydia called Betsy and her children whores and thieves and said that, "burning is too good for them." Although the defendants were found guilty, the damages Mrs. Warner were received was only one cent.
Medicine
Physicians also sued to counteract rumors of their malpractice. Dr. Oliver Fuller of Kent sued another Kent physician Benjamin Chase in 1770 for defaming his character and damaging his reputation. Chase was heard to say that Fuller's "devilish" medicine had killed Simon Geer's wife, and that he would never prescribe such things. Fuller prevailed and was awarded $2 damages.
Robert North, a transient who held himself out as a trained physician, was hired to treat Mrs. Avis Colver of Litchfield, the wife of Joshua Colver. In 1762 he dosed her with physick, making her quite ill. Depositions in the file reveal that North was in fact trained as a carpenter, but he had been unable to make a living in New York at that trade. The depositions in this case provide a remarkable amount of detail on the practice of medicine at the time.
Smallpox was a scourge that was feared by all throughout the early years of Litchfield County's existence, in part due to the fact that the cause of the disease and how it spread were unknown. The Connecticut Colony passed a law in 1732 requiring all dogs to be destroyed in any town where smallpox was suspected; this law stayed on the books until the early 19th century. By the middle of the century, the state of knowledge about the disease and its prevention had advanced. Benjamin Franklin published a treatise while in London in 1759 titled "Some Account of the Success of Inoculation for the Smallpox in England and America," and Connecticut law was amended in 1760 to permit inoculation with the virus. However, this could only take place after two-thirds of the town's voter's approved, and those involved were required to be quarantined, either voluntarily or by force, in the same manner as those who acquired the disease through other means.
Smallpox broke out in Litchfield County in 1761, and there are a number of cases that provide insight into changing attitudes toward the disease. The King's Attorney filed three suits against Salisbury residents Amos Bird, Richard Brownson and Katharine Marsh for voluntarily receiving smallpox by inoculation "to the great terror of His Majesty's subjects.". The defendants were found not guilty. However, suits against Jonathan Hunter of Sharon, accused of leaving a house where smallpox infection was present although ordered to stay and nurse the widow Eleanor Crocker and Daniel Champion of Sharon, accused of throwing down a fence erected around Ensign Thomas Austin's house where smallpox existed, prevailed.
But even in 1801, physician Vine Utley of Winchester was charged with inoculating his wife Rebecca against smallpox without a license. By 1830, however, inoculation only appeared in the courts in allegations of malpractice, as when Harriet Ann Landon of Salisbury, a minor, sued Dr. Asahel Humphrey of Salisbury for malpractice. Landon claimed that Humphrey injured her while inoculating her for "kine pock" by cutting a tendon, ligament and nerve at her elbow, causing her to lose the use of her arm.
Amusements
Entertainments of varying sorts can be found in the criminal cases, including playing at dice and charging admission to see performances of rope dancing and other feats of dexterity. One African-American husband and wife were charged with keeping a house of bawdry and Polly French of Salisbury seems to have been a dominatrix, charged with "restraining, correcting [,] suppressing & punishing Rogues &other lewd [emphasis original] & idle dissolute persons."
In 1794 the state dropped a case against "Merryman" who, with his servant Don Pedro Clores, exhibited tightrope walking and other "feats of uncommon dexterity... tending to collect together spectators to gratify vain and useless curiosity" in Litchfield. The newspapers of the day contained large announcements of the spectacle, which seems to have been popular with area residents.
While Hiram Walters was charged with running an illegal lottery in 1823, legal lotteries, e.g., those approved by the General Assembly, were a popular tool to raise constructions funds for churches and turnpikes. Disputes arose about prizes and payouts, though. The Bridgewater Society lottery seems to have been particularly ill managed, and the committee (Andrew Minor and Abijah Treat of New Milford and Truman Burch of Brookfield) had a number of suits filed against them.
Then as now, boys would be boys, and instances of goofing off can be found in the court records. Hiram Tyrol, apprenticed to Hezekiah Treadwell to learn house joinery and cabinet making, played at "unlawful games" instead of working at his tasks. John Roberts, a minor of Barkhamsted, and his friends gathered in the street in Barkhamsted on April 1, 1831, a day appointed by the Governor for public fasting, to play "games of sport and recreation called Ball and Quoit." Barkhamsted seems to have been a hotbed of such behavior: the State brought charges against Ralsemon Taylor, Sylvester Brown, Harlow Gillet and Henry Brown for breach of peace for assembling to play ball, cards, dice and tables, drink and carouse.
Arrangement
At some point before the records were received by the Connecticut state Archives, they were rearranged. The original arrangement was by year and court session, with each file identified by a docket number. This arrangement scheme is reflected in the contemporaneous record books listed below.
The papers contained in Files, however, are now arranged chronologically by year, merging the year's court sessions into one run. Within the year, individual cases are arranged alphabetically by the plaintiff's surname. The 2001-2004 Court Records Project has maintained this organization.
For criminal cases, the plaintiff name varies by time period. Up to the Revolutionary War, suits were filed by the King's Attorney and the cases were styled: Rex versus the defendant. For about ten years after the start of the war, look under Gov[ernor] & Co[mpany] for criminal matters. By 1784, criminal cases were brought on behalf of the State [of Connecticut].
Related Material
Additional information can be found in the following:
Litchfield County Court Index to Records, 1751-1855 (11 volumes). See container list Litchfield County No. 1. The Index to Records is a master index to all the volumes, with entries by case name.
Litchfield County Court Records, 1751-1855 (22 volumes). See container list Litchfield County No. 2.
Litchfield County Count Dockets, 1759-1855 (19 volumes). See container list Litchfield County No. 6.
Litchfield County Court Executions, 1768-1855 (5 volumes). See container list Litchfield County No. 4.
Litchfield County Court Appeals, 1798-1854 (5 volumes); See Guide to the Records of the Judicial Department.
Litchfield County Court Defaults, 1798-1855 (16 volumes). See container list Litchfield County No. 7.
Litchfield County. County Court. Papers by Subject. See separate finding aid. Papers by Subject is an artificial collection consisting of materials removed from Litchfield County Court Files series by State Library staff after the records were received from the Litchfield court. Papers by Subject consists of records in certain subject categories that were removed from Litchfield County Court Files as State Library staff reorganized them in the 1920s or 1930s. These artificial collections were pulled together to assist researchers by identifying material relating to topics of interest. For some subject categories, not all items were identified or removed by the processors. The 2001-2004 Court Records Project transferred many records from Files to Papers by Subject. However, isolated items remain in Files, particularly in these categories: Conservators & Guardians, Costs, Executions, Licenses and Travel records relating to highways, bridges and turnpikes. To some extent, this reflects organization of the records. For example, in earlier years, Costs and Executions are often found interfiled with the court case to which they apply.
Closely related records are those of the Litchfield County Superior Court. This court heard appeals from cases decided by the county court and the bulk of cases heard by the Superior Court for each county consisted of appeals from the lower court.
In addition, many of the cases heard by the County Court originated in the local justice court, convened by the Justices of the Peace of each town. For more information about Justice of the Peace Courts, and for a list of the State Library's holdings, please see Guide to the Records of the Judicial Department, Second Edition, pages 57-61.
If a researcher is interested in records relating to will or estates, please check the Probate Court Records (RG 004). Land records for Connecticut towns can provide further information for matters relating to real estate. More importantly for the researcher, most land records have been indexed by both the Grantor (owner or seller) and Grantee (buyer or person with a claim to the property). In Connecticut, property deeds are recorded in the records of the town where the land is located, rather than on a county basis as is common in most parts of the country. The State Library has an extensive collection of microfilmed land record volumes and indexes from towns throughout the state.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. County Court (Litchfield County)
Subjects:
County courts -- Connecticut -- Litchfield County -- History; Connecticut -- History -- Sources; Connecticut. County Court (Litchfield County) -- History; Connecticut. Judicial Dept. -- History
Document Types:
Civil court records; Criminal Court records; Judicial records
Restrictions on Access
Many of the papers found in Files for the Litchfield County Court are fragile and they must be handled with great care. Photocopies have been inserted in place of originals for materials on African Americans, Native Americans, and for other items considered to be particularly valuable or vulnerable.
See the policy.
Provenance
The county clerk was responsible for gathering, organizing, and preserving the records for the Litchfield County Court. They were transferred to the Connecticut State Library in 1921.
Container List
- Files, 1751-1855
  - 1751-1752
    - Abbe-Wright (Box 1, Folder 1-16)
  - 1753 (Box 1)
    - Abbe-Bellowes (Box 1, Folder 17-20)
    - Benton-Unidentified (Box 2)
  - 1754
    - Abbott-Sundry (Box 3)
    - Swan-Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 1-4)
  - 1755 (Box 4)
    - Adams-Welch (Box 4, Folder 5-20)
    - Weller-Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1756 (Box 5)
    - Adams-Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 2-14)
  - 1757 (Box 5)
    - Allen-Helenbeck (Box 5, Folder 15-20)
    - Holloway-Unidentified (Box 6, Folder 1-10)
  - 1758 (Box 6)
    - Adam-Knowls (Box 6, Folder 11-20)
    - Lawrence-Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 1-9)
  - 1759 (Box 7)
    - Adams-Litchfield (Box 7, Folder 10-18)
    - Livingston-Unidentified (Box 8, Folder 1-11)
  - 1760 (Box 8)
    - Addams-Hinman (Box 8, Folder 12-18)
    - Hitchcock-Unidentified (Box 9)
  - 1761
    - Allen-Hide (Box 10)
    - Hill-Skilton (Box 11)
    - Smedley-Unidentidied (Box 12, Folder 1-10)
  - 1762 (Box 12)
    - Abbe-Camp (Box 12, Folder 11-20)
    - Canaan-Hopkins (Box 13)
    - Hopkins-Richmond (Box 14)
    - Robards-Unidentified (Box 15, Folder 1-13)
  - 1763 (Box 15)
    - Abbott-Bingham (Box 15, Folder 14-20)
    - Bird-Hinman (Box 16)
    - Hoffman-Ray (Box 17)
    - Read-Unidentified (Box 18, Folder 1-14)
  - 1764 (Box 18)
    - Adams-Bayard (Box 18, Folder 15-20)
    - Beach-Governor (Box 19)
    - Grant-Moss (Box 20)
    - Munger-Westover (Box 21)
    - White-Unidentified (Box 22, Folder 1-4)
  - 1765 (Box 22)
    - Allen-Dixon (Box 22, Folder 5-20)
    - Doud-Moody (Box 23)
    - Munger-Thomlison (Box 24)
    - Thomlinson-Unidentified (Box 25, Folder 1-8)
  - 1766 (Box 25)
    - Averet-Kelsey (Box 25, Folder 9-20)
    - Kent-Undated (Box 26)
  - 1767 (Box 26)
    - Allen-Diems (Box 26, Folder 12-20)
    - Donaghy-Tomlinson (Box 27)
    - Tomlinson-Unidentified (Box 28, Folder 1-7)
  - 1768 (Box 28)
    - Adams-Governor (Box 28, Folder 8-20)
    - Grant-Woodward (Box 29)
    - Woodworth-Unidentified (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - 1769 (Box 30)
    - Abernethy-Orton (Box 30, Folder 2-20)
    - Painter-Unidentified (Box 31, Folder 1-12)
  - 1770 (Box 31)
    - Adams-Chandler (Box 31, Folder 13-20)
    - Chandler-Sacket (Box 32)
    - Salisbury-Unidentified (Box 33, Folder 1-11)
  - 1771 (Box 33)
    - Abbot-Fuller (Box 33, Folder 12-20)
    - Gay-Stannard (Box 34)
    - Starr-Unidentified (Box 35, Folder 1-7)
  - 1772 (Box 35)
    - Ackley-Butler (Box 35, Folder 8-20)
    - Canaan-Kilborn (Box 36)
    - Kingman-Sheldon (Box 37)
    - Sheldon-Undated (Box 38, Folder 1-15)
  - 1773 (Box 38)
    - Abernarthy-Baldwin (Box 38, Folder 16-20)
    - Barbur-Hazard (Box 39)
    - Hide-Pond (Box 40)
    - Pratt-Wheeler (Box 41)
    - White-Unidentified (Box 42, Folder 1-3)
  - 1774 (Box 42)
    - Adams-Catlin (Box 42, Folder 4-20)
    - Catlin-Hoffman (Box 43)
    - Hopkins-Prindle (Box 45)
    - Punderson-Vosburgh (Box 45)
    - Vaughn-Unidentified (Box 46, Folder 1-7)
  - 1775 (Box 46)
    - Abbott-Clarke (Box 46, Folder 8-20)
    - Cockran-Pickett (Box 47)
    - Pitcher-Unidentified (Box 48, Folder 1-15)
  - 1776 (Box 48)
    - Agard-Kent (Box 48, Folder 16-20)
    - Kilborn-Woodbury (Box 49, Folder 1-7)
  - 1777 (Box 49)
    - Africa-Smith (Box 49, Folder 8-20)
    - Starr-Unidentified (Box 50, Folder 1-3)
  - 1778 (Box 50)
    - Atwood-Winchester (Box 50, Folder 4-15)
  - 1779 (Box 50)
    - Abbot-Freeman (Box 50, Folder 16-20)
    - Frisbie-Unidentified (Box 51, Folder 1-16)
  - 1780 (Box 51)
    - Adams-Canfield (Box 51, Folder 17-20)
    - Carrington-Unidentified (Box 52)
  - 1781
    - Adams-Cook (Box 53)
    - Cooley-Lyman (Box 54)
    - McLean-Smith (Box 55)
    - Smith-Unidentified (Box 56, Folder 1-13)
  - 1782 (Box 56)
    - Adams-Bennett (Box 56, Folder 14-20)
    - Bennett-Field (Box 57)
    - Foot-Lord (Box 58)
    - Lynde-Shethar (Box 59)
    - Yale-Unidentified (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - 1783 (Box 61)
    - Adams-Bronson (Box 61, Folder 2-20)
    - Brown-Fox (Box 62)
    - Gaplpin-Kettell (Box 63)
    - Knowles-Ross (Box 64)
    - Ross-Tomlinson (Box 65)
    - Tomlinson-Unidentified (Box 66, Folder 1-13)
  - 1784 (Box 66)
    - Adams-Baker (Box 66, Folder 14-20)
    - Balcom-Cutler (Box 67)
    - Darling-Kingsbury (Box 68)
    - Knickerbacor-Richards (Box 69)
    - Richards-Tyler (Box 70)
    - Van Ness-Unidentified (Box 71, Folder 1-9)
  - 1785 (Box 71)
    - Abernethy-Beach (Box 71, Folder 10-20)
    - Beach-Griffin (Box 72)
    - Hall-New Milford (Box 73)
    - Nickelson-Thomas (Box 74)
    - Thorpe-Unidentified (Box 75, Folder 1-9)
  - 1786 (Box 75)
    - Ackley-Bissell (Box 75, Folder 10-20)
    - Blaklee-Long (Box 76)
    - Lord-Smith (Box 77)
    - Stannard-Unidentified (Box 78, Folder 1-10)
  - 1787 (Box 78)
    - Adams-Bisco (Box 78, Folder 11-20)
    - Bissell-Johnson (Box 79)
    - Johnson-Simpson (Box 80)
    - Skinner-Unidentified (Box 81, Folder 1-13)
  - 1788 (Box 81)
    - Abels-Bacon (Box 81, Folder 14-20)
    - Baker-Deming (Box 82)
    - Deming-Livingston (Box 83)
    - Lloyd-Smith (Box 84)
    - Smith-Unidentified (Box 85, Folder 1-18)
  - 1789 (Box 85)
    - Adams-Atwood (Box 85, Folder 19-20)
    - Atwood-Desbroses (Box 86)
    - Dickinson-Mansell (Box 87)
    - Marsh-Smith (Box 88)
    - Smith-Unidentified (Box 89, Folder 1-14)
  - 1790 (Box 89)
    - Adams-Boardman (Box 89, Folder 15-20)
    - Bogardus-Lane (Box 90)
    - Lane-Smith (Box 91)
    - Smith-Unidentified (Box 92, Folder 1-11)
  - 1791 (Box 92)
    - Adams-Canfield (Box 92, Folder 12-20)
    - Carpenter-Lewis (Box 93)
    - Lilee-Stork (Box 94)
    - Storm-Yale (Box 95, Folder 1-7)
  - 1792 (Box 95)
    - Ackley-Chittenden (Box 95, Folder 8-20)
    - Chittenden-Judd (Box 96)
    - Keep-Ruggles (Box 97)
    - Sackett-Unidentified (Box 98, Folder 1-16)
  - 1793 (Box 98)
    - Adams-Bacon (Box 98, Folder 17-20)
    - Bacon-Fuller (Box 99)
    - Garritt-Penfield (Box 100)
    - Pepoon-Whittlesey (Box 101)
    - Wickwire-Unidentified (Box 102, Folder 1-2)
  - 1794 (Box 102)
    - Adams-Canfield (Box 102, Folder 3-20)
    - Carpenter-Holley (Box 103)
    - Holley-Porter (Box 104)
    - Post-Young (Box 105)
  - 1795
    - Adams-Church (Box 106)
    - Church-Judd (Box 107)
    - Judson-Sherman (Box 108)
    - Shotwell-Unidentified (Box 109, Folder 1-15)
  - 1796 (Box 109)
    - Adams-Bacon (Box 109, Folder 16-20)
    - Baldwin-Fairchild (Box 110)
    - Fancher-Pearsall (Box 112)
    - Peck-Wadsworth (Box 113)
    - Wadsworth-Wright (Box 113, Folder 1-5)
  - 1797 (Box 113)
    - Adams-Buell (Box 113, Folder 6-20)
    - Buell-Gleason (Box 114)
    - Giddings-Lombard (Box 115)
    - Loomis-Smith (Box 116)
    - Southbury-Unidentified (Box 117)
  - 1798
    - Akins-Buell (Box 118)
    - Bulford-Douglas (Box 119)
    - Driggs-Johnson (Box 120)
    - Johnson-Neely (Box 121)
    - New Hartford-Smedly (Box 122)
    - Smith-Wells (Box 123)
    - Wessells-Wright (Box 124, Folder 1-5)
  - 1799 (Box 124)
    - Akins-Boardman (Box 124, Folder 6-20)
    - Boardman-Church (Box 125)
    - Church-Gibbs (Box 126)
    - Giles-Landon (Box 127)
    - Landon-Moore (Box 128)
    - Morey-Royce (Box 129)
    - Rudd-Tallmadge (Box 130)
    - Tallmadge-Young (Box 131, Folder 1-18)
  - 1800 (Box 131)
    - Abbott-Atwater (Box 131, Folder 19-20)
    - Atwood-Broome (Box 132)
    - Brown-Cutler (Box 133)
    - Cutler-Haskell (Box 134)
    - Haviland-Marshall (Box 135)
    - Martin-Rowe (Box 136)
    - Rowlee-Warner (Box 137)
    - Warner-Young (Box 138, Folder 1-3)
  - 1801 (Box 138)
    - Abernathy-Canfield (Box 138, Folder 4-20)
    - Canfield-Howes (Box 139)
    - Hubbard-Prndle (Box 140)
    - Prior-Wardwell (Box 141)
    - Warner-Young (Box 142, Folder 1-7)
  - 1802 (Box 142)
    - Abeck-Canfield (Box 142, Folder 8-20)
    - Canfield-Humphrey (Box 143)
    - Humphrey-Prior (Box 144)
    - Pritchard-Wakeman (Box 145)
    - Walker-Wright (Box 146, Folder 1-7)
  - 1803 (Box 146)
    - Adams-Bowne (Box 146, Folder 8-20)
    - Bradley-Conklin (Box 147)
    - Cook-Judson (Box 148)
    - Kellogg-Nott (Box 149)
    - Oconor-Stevens (Box 150)
    - Stiles-Unidentified (Box 151, Folder 1-12)
  - 1804 (Box 151)
    - Abernathy-Blakesley (Box 151, Folder 13-20)
    - Boardman-Collar (Box 152)
    - Collier-Johnson (Box 153)
    - Johnson-Orsborn (Box 154)
    - Orvis-Sterling (Box 155)
    - Stevens-Young (Box 156, Folder 1-16)
  - 1805 (Box 156)
    - Abbot-Bacon (Box 156, Folder 17-20)
    - Bacon-Chittenden (Box 157)
    - Chittenden-Holabird (Box 158)
    - Holcomb-Nettleton (Box 159)
    - Norton-Rockwell (Box 160)
    - Rockwell-Young (Box 161)
  - 1806
    - Adams-Chittenden (Box 162)
    - Chittenden-Hopkins (Box 163)
    - Hough-Nott (Box 164)
    - Nott-State (Box 165)
    - State-Young (Box 166, Folder 1-18)
  - 1807 (Box 166)
    - Abell-Allen (Box 166, Folder 19-20)
    - Andrews-Cameron (Box 167)
    - Camp-Goshen (Box 168)
    - Grant-Moseley (Box 169)
    - Moulten- St. John (Box 170)
    - St. John-Yale (Box 171)
  - 1808
    - Abel-Beecher (Box 172)
    - Beecher-Chittenden (Box 173)
    - Chittenden-Gay (Box 174)
    - Gaylord-Lamson (Box 175)
    - Landon-Pettibone (Box 176)
    - Phelps-Sanford (Box 177)
    - Sawyer=Walter (Box 178)
    - Warren-Yale (Box 179, Folder 1-9)
  - 1809 (Box 179)
    - Abel-Beecher (Box 179, Folder 10-20)
    - Beecher-Chittenden (Box 180)
    - Chittenden-Eno (Box 181)
    - Ensign-Hull (Box 182)
    - Humphraville-Mansfield (Box 183)
    - Manville-Reed (Box 184)
    - Reed0Studley (Box 185)
    - Sutcliff-Young (Box 186)
  - 1810
    - Abell-Calhoon (Box 187)
    - Calhoon-Fenn (Box 188)
    - Fenn-Johnston (Box 189)
    - Jones-Northrop (Box 190)
    - Norton-Skinner (Box 191)
    - Slosson-Young (Box 192)
  - 1811
    - Abernethy-Calhoon (Box 193)
    - Calhoon-Curtis (Box 194)
    - Dakin-Heacock (Box 195)
    - Hendryx-Lusk (Box 196)
    - Lusk-Phelps (Box 197)
    - Phelps-State (Box 198)
    - State-Woodward (Box 199, Folder 1-17)
  - 1812 (Box 199)
    - Abbott-Barlow (Box 199, Folder 18-20)
    - Barnard-Colebrook (Box 200)
    - Cornstock-Hall (Box 201)
    - Hall-Mallery (Box 202)
    - Marshall-Seymour (Box 203)
    - Seymour-Wright (Box 204)
  - 1813
    - Adam-Church (Box 205)
    - Clarke-Hart (Box 206)
    - Harvey-Minott (Box 207)
    - Mitchell-Sterling (Box 208)
    - Stickles-Yale (Box 209, Folder 1-12)
  - 1814 (Box 209)
    - Abernethy-Bradley (Box 209, Folder 13-20)
    - Brewster-Gould (Box 210)
    - Lewis-Rosseter (Box 212)
    - Rowley-Wilcox (Box 213)
    - Wilcox-Wright (Box 214, Folder 1-4)
  - 1815 (Box 214)
    - Aakins-Bradley (Box 214, Folder 5-20)
    - Brewster-Cornwall (Box 215)
    - Cowles-Gunn (Box 216)
    - Gunn-Lambert (Box 217)
    - Lamson-Mitchell (Box 218)
    - Morison-Raymond (Box 219)
    - Reed-State (Box 220)
    - Sterling-Youngs (Box 221, Folder 1-19)
  - 1816 (Box 221)
    - Abbott-Adam (Box 221, Folder 20)
    - Alexander-Bostwick (Box 222)
    - Botsford-Chapin (Box 223)
    - Chapman-Delavan (Box 224)
    - Deming-Griswold (Box 225)
    - Gross-Hubbard (Box 226)
    - Hubbell-Lamb (Box 227)
    - Lamb-Mills (Box 228)
    - Mills-Porter (Box 229)
    - Porter-Shelton (Box 230)
    - Shelton-Sturdevant (Box 231)
    - Sugden-Winchester (Box 232)
    - Wolcott-Unidentified (Box 233, Folder 1-2)
  - 1817 (Box 233)
    - Abernathy-Blake (Box 233, Folder 3-20)
    - Blake-Catlin (Box 234)
    - Catlin-Cook (Box 235)
    - Cook-Garnsey (Box 236)